{
  "title": "Halloween!",
  "listOfQuestions": [
    {
      "question": "What vegetable was originally used to carve Jack-o'-lanterns?",
      "correctAnswer": "Turnip",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Pumpkin", "Potato", "Radish"],
      "timeout": 15
    },
    {
      "question": "Which Halloween monster is known for counting garlic?",
      "correctAnswer": "Vampire",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Werewolf", "Zombie", "Mummy"],
      "timeout": 15
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the classic Halloween song that starts with the lyric 'It's close to midnight'? ",
      "correctAnswer": "Thriller",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Ghostbusters", "Monster Mash", "Somebody's Watching Me"],
      "timeout": 15
    },
    {
      "question": "In which country did Halloween originate?",
      "correctAnswer": "Ireland",
      "wrongAnswers": ["USA", "Mexico", "Scotland"],
      "timeout": 15
    },
    {
      "question": "What do you traditionally bob for during Halloween?",
      "correctAnswer": "Apples",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Potatoes", "Peaches", "Plums"],
      "timeout": 15
    },
    {
      "question": "What color is often associated with Halloween?",
      "correctAnswer": "Orange",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Blue", "Red", "Green"],
      "timeout": 15
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of creature is Dracula?",
      "correctAnswer": "Vampire",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Werewolf", "Zombie", "Ghost"],
      "timeout": 15
    },
    {
      "question": "Which 18+ Halloween film features a Bogey Man?",
      "correctAnswer": "Halloween",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Friday the 13th", "A Nightmare on Elm Street", "Scream"],
      "timeout": 15
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the day after Halloween known as?",
      "correctAnswer": "All Saints' Day",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Day of the Dead", "November 1st", "Dia de los Muertos"],
      "timeout": 15
    },
    {
      "question": "Which animal is commonly associated with witchcraft?",
      "correctAnswer": "Cat",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Dog", "Owl", "Raven"],
      "timeout": 15
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a common Halloween prank?",
      "correctAnswer": "Egging houses",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Toilet papering trees", "Hiding candy", "Dressing in a costume"],
      "timeout": 15
    },
    {
      "question": "What candy is known for its peanut butter filling?",
      "correctAnswer": "Reese's Peanut Butter Cups",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Snickers", "Twix", "M&M's"],
      "timeout": 15
    },
    {
      "question": "Which phobia refers to a fear of Halloween?",
      "correctAnswer": "Samhainophobia",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Necrophobia", "Cacophobia", "Phasmophobia"],
      "timeout": 15
    },
    {
      "question": "What do you say when you go door-to-door asking for treats?",
      "correctAnswer": "Trick or treat!",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Happy Halloween!", "Give me candy!", "Boo!"],
      "timeout": 15
    },
    {
      "question": "Which horror author is known for writing 'It' and 'The Shining'?",
      "correctAnswer": "Stephen King",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Edgar Allan Poe", "H.P. Lovecraft", "Clive Barker"],
      "timeout": 15
    },
    {
      "question": "What do you call a gathering of witches?",
      "correctAnswer": "Coven",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Huddle", "Group", "Assembly"],
      "timeout": 15
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the common name for the evening before Halloween?",
      "correctAnswer": "Mischief Night",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Eve of Hallows", "All Hallows' Eve", "Devil's Night"],
      "timeout": 15
    },
    {
      "question": "Which popular Halloween candy is known for its soft texture and spooky shape?",
      "correctAnswer": "Marshmallow Peeps",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Candy Corn", "Gummy Worms", "Chocolate Bars"],
      "timeout": 15
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the top-selling candy during Halloween?",
      "correctAnswer": "Candy Corn",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Snickers", "M&M's", "Skittles"],
      "timeout": 15
    },
    {
      "question": "What does a ghost typically represent?",
      "correctAnswer": "The spirit of a deceased person",
      "wrongAnswers": ["A monster", "A witch", "A zombie"],
      "timeout": 15
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the term for a fear of spiders?",
      "correctAnswer": "Arachnophobia",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Entomophobia", "Chiroptophobia", "Thanatophobia"],
      "timeout": 15
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the vampire-like creature in Filipino folklore?",
      "correctAnswer": "Aswang",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Chupacabra", "Banshee", "Wendigo"],
      "timeout": 15
    },
    {
      "question": "What are Halloween-themed parties often referred to as?",
      "correctAnswer": "Spooktaculars",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Haunt Nights", "Boo Bash", "Ghost Gatherings"],
      "timeout": 15
    },
    {
      "question": "Which candy has a connection to Halloween and is commonly given out?",
      "correctAnswer": "Candy Corn",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Twizzlers", "Swedish Fish", "Skittles"],
      "timeout": 15
    },
    {
      "question": "What creature is often depicted as a flying mammal associated with Halloween?",
      "correctAnswer": "Bat",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Owl", "Crow", "Raven"],
      "timeout": 15
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of dance is often associated with Halloween parties?",
      "correctAnswer": "Monster Mash",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Macarena", "Cha-Cha", "Moonwalk"],
      "timeout": 15
    },
    {
      "question": "What is one of the most common Halloween costumes?",
      "correctAnswer": "Ghost",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Pirate", "Princess", "Superhero"],
      "timeout": 15
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name for the carved pumpkins used at Halloween?",
      "correctAnswer": "Jack-o'-lanterns",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Munchkin Munchers", "Ghost Gourds", "Spooky Squashes"],
      "timeout": 15
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of tree is typically associated with Halloween?",
      "correctAnswer": "Broom Tree",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Cypress", "Willow", "Pine"],
      "timeout": 15
    },
    {
      "question": "In which animated film did a character named Jack Skellington appear?",
      "correctAnswer": "The Nightmare Before Christmas",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Hocus Pocus", "Coraline", "Frankenweenie"],
      "timeout": 15
    },
    {
      "question": "If you see a spider on Halloween, what is it said to represent?",
      "correctAnswer": "The spirit of a loved one",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Bad luck", "A warning", "A tracking device"],
      "timeout": 15
    },
    {
      "question": "What do skeletons often symbolize?",
      "correctAnswer": "Death",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Life", "Love", "Joy"],
      "timeout": 15
    },
    {
      "question": "Which famous magician died on Halloween?",
      "correctAnswer": "Harry Houdini",
      "wrongAnswers": ["David Copperfield", "Dynamo", "Criss Angel"],
      "timeout": 15
    },
    {
      "question": "What is traditionally used to ward off vampires?",
      "correctAnswer": "Garlic",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Holy Water", "Silver", "Salt"],
      "timeout": 15
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of mythical creature is a Mummy?",
      "correctAnswer": "Corpse wrapped in bandages",
      "wrongAnswers": ["A blood sucking person", "A dead person who eats brains", "A dead spirit"],
      "timeout": 15
    }
  ],
  "time given": "15"
}

